Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Audiovisual Recordings, 177683
  - Subseries A: The Soul of Reason Audio Recordings, 248731
    - Higgins, Chester, Jr. -- photographer., 1974 August 13; RG9.8-49; 177917; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 49)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Chester Higgins, Jr. discuss the role and impact of the Black photographer.
    - Williams, Bob and Ronald Lee Gaudreau -- Executive Vice President of the New York City Bicentennial Corporation, and the Director of Community Programs for the New York City Bicentennial Corporation., 1974 August 20; RG9.8-48; 177836; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 52, Folder 48)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Bob Williams, and Ronald Lee Gaudreau discuss New York City events surrounding the American Bicentennial.
    - Killens, John O. -- author of the historic novel Young Blood., 1974 August 27; RG9.8-79; 177998; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 41, Folder 79)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and novelist John O. Killens discuss the state of Black writing.
    - Mitchem, Dr. John -- Chairman of the Department of Compensatory Programs at Baruch Collge of the City University of New York., 1974 September 4; RG9.8-189; 178164; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 55, Folder 189)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. John Mitchem discuss the decline in college enrollment among Black and Puerto Rican youth, as well as issues these communities face within the university and what services are available to alleviate these issues.
    - Pinero, Miguel -- playwright and author of Short Eyes., 1974 September 10; RG9.8-46; 177834; Format: Reel TRT: 28:55 (Box 52, File 46)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Miguel Pinero discuss Pinero's play Short Eyes.
    - Meminger, Dean -- American basketball player of the New York Knicks and the Atlanta Hawks., 1974 September 17; RG9.8-47; 177835; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 52, Folder 47)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dean Meminger discuss how Black athletes are contributing to their communities.
    - Broughton, Modeen and Cheryl Goggins -- Coordinator and Assistant Coordinator of the Congressional Black Caucus Dinner., 1974 September 24; RG9.8-45; 177833; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 45)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Modeen Broughton, and Cheryl Goggins discuss the significance of the Black Caucus Dinner, an important political affair of the year for Black officials, and how the funds raised by the event are utilized.
    - Neal, James -- representative from National Artists Coalition, Inc., 1974 October 2; RG9.8-192; 178167; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 55, Folder 192)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and James Neale discuss themes in contemporary Black art, as well as how the public can help Black artists.
    - Gidron, Dick -- business owner of Dick Gidron Cadillacs., 1974 October 9; RG9.8-191; 178166; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 55, Folder 191)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dick Gidron discuss the scope and meaning of Gidron's business Dick Gidron Cadillacs, which became the first Black-owned Cadillac dealership in New York City when it opened in the Bronx in 1972.
    - Sandler, Joan -- Executive Director of the Black Theatre Alliance., 1974 October 9; RG9.8-187; 178162; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 55, Folder 187)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Joan Sandler discuss the fall season of Black theater in New York, as well as what goals can be met when theaters come together through collectives like the Black Theatre Alliance.
    - Weathers, Diane and Camille Billops -- Co-Editor of Black Creation magazine, and faculty member of the art departments at Rutgers University and the City University of New York and contributor to Black Creation., 1974 October 30; RG9.8-183; 178158; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 55, Folder 183, Box Access 14, Disk 17)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Camille Billops, and Diane Weathers discuss the annual issue of Black Creation, a magazine of Black artistic criticism that covers drama, dance, music, poetry, film, literature, art and other areas of the Black arts.
    - Patterson, Basil -- Vice Chairman of the Democratic National Committee., 1974 November 19; RG9.8-44; 177832; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 44)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Basil Patterson discuss the potential impact of the Watergate scandal on Black America.
    - Brown, Courtney -- New York State Division of Human Rights., 1974 November 20; RG9.8-156; 178134; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 156)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Courtney Brown discuss the meaning, quotas, and goals of affirmative action.
    - Artist, Ruth -- interior decorator., 1974 November 26; RG9.8-43; 177831; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 52, Folder 43)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ruth Artist discuss interior decorating.
    - Bryant, Linda -- Director of the Just Above Midtown Gallery., 1974 December 3; RG9.8-42; 177830; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 42)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Linda Bryant discuss the opening of the Just Above Midtown Gallery at 50 West 57 Street, a gallery formed to promote 20th-century Afro-American artists.
    - Mays, Charles and Herb Douglas -- Director of the Black Athletes Hall of Frame, and Vice President of Shefflin Corporation and Chairman of the Board of the Black Athletes Hall of Fame., 1974 December 10; RG9.8-41; 177829; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 41)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and athletes Charles Mays and Herb Douglas discuss the formation and significance of the Black Athletes Hall of Fame.
    - Jeffries, Dr. Leonard -- Director of Black Studies at the City College of New York., 1974 December 11; RG9.8-155; 178133; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 155)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Leonard Jeffries discuss the future of Black Studies and which courses seem to be most successful for students.
    - Goodwin, Steven -- Investment Executive and Investment Counselor at Hayden Stone and Company., 1974 December 17; RG9.8-40; 177717; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 40)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Steven Goodwin discuss the basic principles of the stock market and why the Black community should be interested in the market.
    - Jordan, Richard -- Director of National Urban Services for the Boys Club of America., 1975 February 18; RG9.8-89; 178061; Format: Reel TRT: 28:55 (Box 41, Folder 89)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Richard Jordan discuss the commitment of the Boys Clubs of America to inner-city, minority youth.
    - Kornblum, William, Herb Cables, and Frances Gibson -- representatives from the Gateway National Recreational Center of the National Park Service., 1975 February 25; RG9.8-147; 178125; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 147)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., William Kornblum, Herb Cables, and Frances Gibson discuss plans for the federally funded Gateway National Park.
    - Zollner, Joy -- representative from the organization RAINS (Relief for Africans in Need in the Sahel)., 1975 March 1; RG9.8-165; 178143; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 165)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Joy Zollner discuss how the organization RAINS (Relief for Africans in Need in the Sahel) is addressing the African famine.
    - Edley, Christopher -- Executive Director of the United Negro College Fund., 1975 March 11; RG9.8-148; 178126; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 148)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Christopher Edley discuss ways the United Negro College Fund hopes to help 41 of the 108 Black colleges in America survive during a year of economic and political unrest.
    - Wright, Samuel -- Councilman for 26th Council District in Brooklyn., 1975 March 26; RG9.8-158; 178136; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 158)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Samuel Wright discuss the role of the councilman and reasons why the Black community and Puerto Rican community are not participating more in city affairs.
    - Toote, Dr. Gloria --Assistant Secretary of the United States Department of Housing and Urban Development., 1975 April 8; RG9.8-141; 178118; Format: Reel TRT: 28:00 (Box 53, Folder 141)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Gloria Toote discuss ways laws preventing discrimination in housing can be better enforced.
    - Yancy, Joe -- track athlete and the co-founder of the New York Pioneer Club., 1975 April 9; RG9.8-157; 178135; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 157)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Joe Yancy discuss Yancy's career in track and an event to honor him at the Waldorf Astoria.
    - Gourdine, Simon -- Deputy Commissioner for the National Basketball Association., 1975 April 14; RG9.8-151; 178129; Format: Reel TRT: 28:10 (Box 53, Folder 151)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Simon Gourdine discuss how Black players have made an indelible impression on basketball.
    - Alexander, Jesse and Fred Hill -- YMCA representatives., 1975 April 22; RG9.8-135; 178112; Format: Reel TRT: 28:10 (Box 53, Folder 135)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Fred Hill, and Jesse Alexander discuss how YMCA facilities have adapted to better serve inner-city communities.
    - Lewis, Ed and Marcia Gillespie -- Publisher and Editor of Essence magazine., 1975 April 23; RG9.8-184; 178159; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 55, Folder 184)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Ed Lewis, and Marcia Gillespie discuss the fifth anniversary of Essence, the first Black woman's magazine.
    - Williams, John A. -- Professor of English at LaGuardia Community College of the City University of New York and author of Mothersill and the Foxes., 1975 April 29; RG9.8-139; 178116; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 139)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and writer John A. Williams discuss his new book Mothersill and the Foxes about the romantic encounters of a Black man in Cleveland and New York.
    - Hinds, Lennox -- National Director of the National Conference of Black Lawyers., 1975 May 13; RG9.8-140; 178117; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 140)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Lennox Hinds discuss how the National Conference of Black Lawyers seeks justice for many minority groups, including Blacks, Hispanics, and the economically-deprived.
    - Loney, Dr. Roderick -- Chairman of the Academic Development Division at Medgar Evers College of the City University of New York., 1975 May 14; RG9.8-152; 178130; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 152)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Roderick Loney discuss what certain special educational programs and open enrollment mean for Black and Puerto Rican students entering college.
    - Holloman, Dr. John -- President of the New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation., 1975 May 28; RG9.8-194; 178169; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 54, Folder 194)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. John Holloman discuss accomplishments and issues of the New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation, the largest health organization in the world at the time.
    - Ward, Douglas Turner -- Director of the Negro Ensemble Company and Producer of First Breeze of Summer., 1975 June 11; RG9.8-105; 178070; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 41, Folder 105)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Douglas Turner Ward discuss the Broadway play First Breeze of Summer, as well as other developments in Black theatre.
    - Batchelor, Ron -- Executive Director of Broad Jump., 1975 June 17; RG9.8-137; 178114; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 137)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ron Batchelor discuss the alternative educational program Broad Jump in Harlem.
    - Archer, Lee -- Director of Equal Opportunity of Affairs of the General Foods Corporation and Chairman of the North Street Capital Corporation., 1975 June 24; RG9.8-39; 177716; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 39)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Lee Archer discuss how Black business executives are coping with the recession.
    - Bullins, Ed -- author of The Taking of Miss Janie., 1975 July 1; RG9.8-38; 177715; Format: Reel TRT:28:50 (Box 40, Folder 38)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ed Bullins discuss Bullin's piece The Taking of Miss Janie, a play about Black and white relations during the 1960s. At the time of their discussion, the play was being performed at the Mitzi Newhouse Theatre in Lincoln Center.
    - King, Angela -- Social Affairs Officer of the United Nations., 1975 July 15; RG9.8-72; 177969; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 72)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Angela King discuss the creation of International Women's Year by the United Nations in order to recognize accomplishments and discuss problems faced by women across the globe.
    - Jones, Martha and Diane Lacey -- Public Relations Director of the Women's Action Alliance, and Special Assistant to the President of the New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation., 1975 July 16; RG9.8-136; 178113; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 136)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Martha Jones, and Diane Lacey discuss Black women's criticisms of the women's movement after 1975 was named International Women's Year.
    - Hamilton, Dr. Charles -- political scientist and President of the Metropolitan Applied Research Center., 1975 August 5; RG9.8-71; 177968; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 71)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Charles Hamilton discuss the future of the Metropolitan Applied Research Center, a non-profit organization concerned with research on matters of urgency for the Black community.
    - Younger, Eddie -- athlete, representative from the New York City Department of Recreation, and a board member for the Harlem Professional, Inc., 1975 August 12; RG9.8-145; 178123; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 145)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Eddie Younger discuss contemporary efforts to honor Black athletes for their accomplishments.
    - Maynard, Joan -- Executive Director of the Society for the Preservation of Weeksville and Bedford-Stuyvesant History., 1975 September 2; RG9.8-70; 177967; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 70)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Joan Maynard discuss Weeksville, a community where freed slaves settled during the first half of the 19th Century. They also speak about the Society for the Preservation of Weeksville and Bedford-Stuyvesant History, which was initially created in order to restore three houses within the original perimeter of Weeksville.
    - Taylor, Emory -- Director of the Harlem Opera Society., 1975 September 9; RG9.8-69; 177956; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 69)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Emory Taylor discuss the history and work of the Harlem Opera Society, which was responsible for 40 performances a year, including two to three Black operas in the New York metropolitan area.
    - Wright, Dr. Stephen -- Vice President of the College Entrance Examination Board., 1975 September 17; RG9.8-153; 178131; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 53, Folder 153)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Stephen Wright discuss higher education opportunities for Black students.
    - Harris, Richard and Sergeant James Hargrove -- President of the Vulcan Society and President of The Guardians Association., 1975 September 23; RG9.8-154; 178132; Format: Reel TRT: 29:45 (Box 53, Folder 154)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Richard Harris, and Sergeant James Hargrove discuss the unique challenges faced by Black policemen and Black firemen within New York City. They also discuss how organizations like The Vulcans and The Guardians attempt to alleviate some of those issues.
    - Sparks, George and William Alston -- Grand Master of the King George Grand Lodge and Publisher of the Long Island Courier., 1975 September 23; RG9.8-144; 178122; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 53, Folder 144)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., George Sparks, and William Alston discuss the role of the Black mason.
    - Dempsey, Ellen, Robert Williams, and Florence Jackson -- two representatives from the New York City Bicentennial Corporation and the Director of Social Studies for New York City Board of Education., 1975 October 1; RG9.8-193; 178168; Format: Reel TRT: 29:45 (Box 55, Folder 193, Box Access 13, Item 11)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Ellen Dempsey, Robert Williams, and Florence Jackson discuss the various school and community projects prompted by the Bicentennial.
    - Lewis, Jerry and Marion Bondurant --Executive Director and Assistant Director of Development for the National Medical Fellowships., 1975 October 15; RG9.8-195; 178171; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 54, Folder 195)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Jerry Lewis, and Marion Bondurant discuss the program and objectives of National Medical Fellowships, which serves minority medical students, especially during their first year of medical school.
    - Rainford, Patricia Luces -- Associate Director of the Bronx Municipal Hospital Center., 1975 October 29; RG9.8-76; 177981; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 41, Folder 76)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Patricia Luces Rainford discuss the future of New York's 18 municipal hospitals during New York's fiscal crisis.
    - Thomas, Franklin -- President of the Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation., 1975 October 29; RG9.8-12; 177693; Format: Reel TRT: 28:00 (Box 40, Folder 12, Box Access 13, Item 9)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Franklin Thomas discuss the accomplishments and the problems of the Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, which was founded in 1967 to assist economic development in Brooklyn's Bedford-Stuyvesant neighborhood.
    - Barron, Allan -- Publisher of Black Sports Magazine., 1975 November 11; RG9.8-68; 177953; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 52, Folder 68)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Allan Barron discuss how sports became a major part of Black life in America.
    - Addison, Gayle -- writer, critic and Associate Professor of English at Baruch College of the City University of New York., 1975 November 12; RG9.8-84; 178006; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 41, Folder 84)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Gayle Addison discuss the status of Black writing.
    - Goodwin, Steven -- Investment Counselor and Option Specialist for U.S. Option International, Inc., 1975 November 12; RG9.8-13; 177694; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Steven Goodwin discuss the status of the stock market in 1975 and the ways in which a decrease in the demand for municipal bonds affected the Black community.
    - Furman, Roger -- playwright and Director of the New Heritage Repertory Theatre in Harlem., 1975 December 10; RG9.8-16; 177700; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Roger Furman discuss Furman's new play Fat Tuesday about Black life in New Orleans during the 1930s, as well as other developments in Black theater.
    - Bailey, Peter -- Associate Editor of Black Enterprise Magazine., 1975; RG9.8-10; 177691; Format: Reel TRT: 29:35 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Peter Bailey discuss the 1975-1976 dance and theater season, including productions on and off Broadway.
    - Harris, Diane, Frances Gibson, and William Kornblum -- Public Involvement Assistant, Recreation Specialist, and a member of the planning board for the Gateway National Recreation Area., 1975; RG9.8-11; 177692; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Diane Harris, Frances Gibson, and William Kornblum discuss planning for the Gateway National Recreation Area, a federal public park.
    - Clark, Sam -- radio personality and producer of the record Black Americans., 1976 January 7; RG9.8-17; 177701; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Sam Clark discuss Clark's record Black Americans, a record that addresses Blacks and the United States Bicentennial, and whether or not the Black man is still fighting the United States government.
    - Frazier, Cliff -- Administrator of Third World Cinema., 1976 January 7; RG9.8-20; 177704; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Cliff Frazier discuss trends in Black filmmaking, including the roles portrayed by Black actors in Black films.
    - Coombs, Orde -- author and critic., 1976 January 13; RG9.8-126; 178104; Format: Reel TRT: 29:25 (Box 50, Folder 126)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Orde Coombs speak about Coombs' tour of the People's Republic of China the previous year.
    - Carr, Ivory -- Assistant Director of Ambulatory Care at Brooklyn Jewish Hospital and Medical Center., 1976 January 14; RG 9.8-18; 177702; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ivory Carr discuss child abuse.
    - Bullock, Kathleen, Mark Millander, and Terry Smith -- students from the New York City Executive High School Intern Program., 1976 January 21; RG9.8-196; 178172; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 54, Folder 196)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and students Kathleen Bullock, Mark Millander, and Terry Smith discuss the professional development opportunities made available by the New York City Executive High School Intern Program.
    - Hutson, Jean Blackwell -- Chief of the Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture., 1976 February 4; RG9.8-22; 177706; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Jean Blackwell Hutson discuss how a grant from the National Endowment for the Humanities allowed the Schomburg Center to gain bibliographic control over its collections. They discuss different aspects of the center's history with the New York Public Library and speak about fundraising efforts for a new, larger structure.
    - Wallace, Robert E. -- Executive Director of the National Interagency Council on Smoking and Health., 1976 February 4; RG9.8-19; 177703; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Robert E. Wallace discuss ways to decrease smoking in the United States.
    - Barnes, Arthur -- President of the New York Urban Coalition., 1976 February 18; RG9.8-159; 178137; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 159)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Arthur Barnes discuss the progress and programs of the New York Urban Coalition, which was founded in the late 1960s in order to address unrest within the Black and Puerto Rican communities.
    - Suggs, Dr. Dolores -- Assistant to the Dean of Student Affairs at the New York University College of Dentistry., 1976 March 3; RG9.8-197; 178173; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 54, Folder 197)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Dolores Suggs discuss what is being done to train more Black men and women to address dental problems in the Black community.
    - Armstead-Johnson, Dr. Helen -- Director of the Afro-American Theater Museum and Professor of English at York College of the City University of New York., 1976 March 23; RG9.8-125; 178103; Format: Reel TRT: 28:35 (Box 50, Folder 125)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Helen Armstead-Johnson discuss the collection Armstead-Johnson has assembled about the development of Afro-American theatre.
    - White, Dr. Herbert -- representative from the New York City Department of Personnel., 1976 April 28; RG9.8-124; 178102; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 50, Folder 124)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Herbert White discuss how recent cutbacks in New York City have had an adverse impact on minority employees.
    - Walker, Dr. Wyatt T. -- Canaan Baptist Church of Harlem., 1976 May 11; RG9.8-73; 177974; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 41, Folder 73)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Wyatt T. Walker discuss the role of the Black church, which, historically, was the most pervasive social force within the Black community.